Guide to the Service Employees International Union Local 585 Records, 1966-1989 AIS.1982.14
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Collection Additions, II.
  - Allegheny County Clerical-Technical Unit, Grievances, 1972-1976 (Box 29, Folder 20-21)
  - Allegheny County Clerical-Technical Unit Chapter Officers, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Allegheny County Clerical-Technical Unit Stewards Minutes, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Allegheny County Clerical-Technical Unit Negotiations, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Allegheny County Clerical-Technical Unit Membership Meeting Notices, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Allegheny County - Newspaper Clippings (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Allegheny County Clerical-Technical Unit Contract, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Allegheny County Clerical-Technical Unit Salary/Classifications, 1975-1979 (Box 18, Folder 27-30)
  - Allegheny County Clerical-Technical Unit Membership Resignations, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Allegheny County Clerical-Technical Unit Negotiations, 1972-1979 (Box 18, Folder 32-33)
  - Allegheny County Clerical-Technical Unit Fringe Benefits, 1975-1978 (Box 18, Folder 34-36)
  - Allegheny County Clerical-Technical Unit Disciplines/Firings, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Allegheny County Clerical-Technical Unit Grievances (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Allegheny County Clerical-Technical Unit Job Description/Classification, 1968-1979 (Box 18, Folder 39-40)
  - Allegheny County Clerical-Technical Unit, Unit Clarification (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Allegheny County Clerical-Technical Unit Lay-Offs, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Allegheny County Clerical-Technical Unit CETA, 1978-1980 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Allegheny County Clerical-Technical Unit Job Bidding (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Allegheny County Clerical-Technical Unit Hours, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Allegheny County Clerical-Technical Unit Membership Meeting Notices, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Allegheny County Clerical-Technical Unit Chapter Offices, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Allegheny County Clerical-Technical Unit Good and Welfare, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Allegheny County Professional Unit Eligibility List Stickers, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Allegheny County Professional Unit Organizational Leaflets, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 50-51)
  - Allegheny County Professional Unit Annotated Eligibility List, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Allegheny County Professional Unit Eligibility List/Voting Sites, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Allegheny County Professional Unit Organizational Mailings, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 54-55)
  - Allegheny County Professional Unit Organization, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 56-57)
  - Elwood City School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Evergreen Nursing Home - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Fayette County - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Lafayette Manor, Inc. - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Forest Hills School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Franklin Area School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Gallatin National Bank - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Harmar Township - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Greene Co. Memorial Township - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - General Braddock - Cafeteria - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - General Braddock School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Highland Area - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Indiana Township - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Jefferson Morgan School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Keystone Oaks School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Kiski Area School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Greater Latrobe School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Leechburg Area School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Greater Latrobe Cafeteria - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Mt. Lebanon School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Mt. Pleasant School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Monsour Medical Center - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - New Kensington Arnold School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - North Braddock Authority - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - North Hills School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - North Star School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Oil City School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Plum Boro School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Penn Trafford School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Peters Twp. S.D. Att M Yates SE - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Point Park College - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Portage School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - South Butler School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Southeastern Green School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - South Park School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Southmoreland School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Trinity Area School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - City of Washington School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Washington P&R Comm. - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Washington School District - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Collective Bargaining Research, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Local 666 - Contract Negotiations, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Local 666 - Gas Employees Union - Negotiations, 1973-1977 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Local 555 - Contract Negotiations, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - "The People's Natural Gas Company Wage Earner Job Descriptions", 1974 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Local 666 - Strike/Negotiations, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Local 999 - "Consolidated Gas Supply Corporation Union Clerical Job Description", 1974 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Local 999 - Negotiations, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - ANGWU, Local 999 - Employment Contract/Certificate of Compliance and Insurance, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - ANGWU, Local 999 - Negotiations, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 10-11)
  - ANGWU, Local 999 - Union's General Correspondence, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Local 999 - Wagner Arbitrations - Grogg Arbitration, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Consolidated Gas Corporation - Settlement Agreement, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - AFL-CIO - Steel Settlement, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Historical Description of Social Security Program/Field Letter-22, 1968-1971 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Peoples Natural Gas - Annual Report/General Correspondence, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Peoples Natural Gas Co. - D-2 Forms, 1969-1970, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Peoples Natural Gas Co. - "Labor Contract: The Peoples Natural Gas Company", 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Local 666 - Negotiations/Research Material, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 20-22)
  - The Peoples Natural Gas Co. - Job Description/Contract, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Westmoreland County - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Washington County - Dues Check-Off, 1978-1980 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Arline Jolles Lotman, Esq. - Biography (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Political Correspondence, 1981, 1983-1984 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Mondale, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Mondale Campaign, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Ed Grystar - Senate Campaign, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Political Contribution Requests, 1982-1984 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Shirley Caldwell - Correspondence and Campaign Materials, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Dale Newman - Biographical Sketch, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - AFL-CIO - Campaign for America's Future, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 9-10)
  - Campaign Materials, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Election Newspaper Clippings, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Beaver County Police Center, 1980-1981 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Beaver County - Court Related Correspondence, 1975-1981 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Beaver County - Insurance Probe, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Beaver County - Jail Guards Correspondence, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Beaver County - Jail Guards Contract, Working Copy, 1974-1974, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Beaver County - Non-court Correspondence, 1975-1980 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Beaver County - Non-court Contract - Working Copy, 1973-1975, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Beaver Valley Geriatrics Center - Correspondence, 1975-1980 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Beaver Valley Geriatrics Center Contract - Signed, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Beaver Valley Geriatrics Center - Information, 1977-1981 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Beaver Valley Geriatrics Center - Working Copy, 1978-1979 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Beaver Valley Geriatrics Center - Contract - Working Copy, 1974, 1981-1984 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Beaver Valley Geriatrics Center - New Hires - Terminations, 1977-1980 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Washington County - List of Employees, 1978-1980 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Washington County Prison - Results of Election, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Washington County - Commissioner's Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Washington County - Court Related Contract - Working Copy, 1973 & 1975 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Washington County - Non-Court Related Contract - Working Copy, 1973, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Washington County Jail - Guard's Correspondence, 1973, 1975, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Washington County Jail - Guards Contract - Working Copy, 1973, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Washington County - Contract Agreement - Working Copy, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Washington County, 1971, 1975-1976, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Washington County - Related Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Washington County - Non-Court Related Correspondence, 1975-1980 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Contract Summaries, 1980-1982 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Correspondence from International, 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Memos From International, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Correspondence to International, 1979-1981 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Eastern Conference Constitution and By-Laws, 1979-1981 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Affiliated Local Unions, 1976-1978 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Contracts, Seniority Lists, 1980-1982 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Southeastern Greene School District - #182, 1980-1983 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Southeastern Greene School District - Agreement - Working Copy, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Southeastern Greene School District - Negotiations, 1971, 1980, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Armstrong County - Agreement, 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Armstrong Health Center - Negotiations, 1980-1981 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Armstrong County - Courthouse Campaign, 1980-1982 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - "Children and Youth Services On-Call Procedure", 1981 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Armstrong Health Center - Agreement, 1980-1981 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Armstrong County - Agreement/Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Armstrong County - Waynesburg College - Maintenance Receipts, 1980-1981 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Waynesburg College - Agreement/Correspondence - Working Copy, 1980-1982 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - ARA Services - Agreement, 1977-1983 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Armstrong County - Armstrong Court House Cards, 1975-1976 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Armstrong School District - District Wages, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - SEIU - Allegheny County - News/General Correspondence, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Rosemary Trump - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Allegheny County - Agreement, Contract, and Correspondence, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Rosemary Trump - Stephen Kotran Scholarship, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - People's Budget Coalition - Correspondence, Membership Forms, Publications, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Rosemary Trump - Correspondence About Plant Closings, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - SEIU/AFL-CIO - Steward Employment Manuals and Instructions (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Public Interest Coalition - Plant Closing Meeting - Harry Boyer Speech, Research, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Westmoreland County - SEIU Seasonal Publications, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Service Employee - Various Editions, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Pittsburgh Business Times, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - 1199 News - Various Editions, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Rosemary Trump - Local 715 News and Correspondence, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Pennsylvania Social Services Union - RE:MEMBER and RE:UNION Pamphlets, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - SEIU - Local News - Local 585 and Local 556, 1980-1981 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - The Voice - Various Editions, 1980-1981 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - AFL-CIO News - Various Editions, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Labor Times - Various Editions, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Labor and the Humanities - Various Editions, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - AFL-CIO - Clerical News Publications - Various, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - The Federationist - Various Editions, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - AFL-CIO/SEIU - Convention - Research and Itinerary, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - The International Teamster - Fitzsimmons Memorial Issue, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Lloyd McBride - Testimonial Dinner Program, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Rosemary Trump - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Steward Training, 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Active Member List, 1975-1979 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - SEIU Local 585 - "Fair Share" Dues Restructuring Ballot, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Election Materials (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Staff Meetings, 1977-1979 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - SEIU Local 585 - General Correspondence (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - AFSCME-ALLIANCE - Correspondence/Reports, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - AFl-CIO - Tax Mapping, 1979-1980 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Staff Assignments, 1975-1978 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Anne T. Lucas - Grievance, 1980-1981 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Elwood City Cafeteria - Contract - Working Copy, 1975-1976 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Elwood City - Custodians - Contract Negotiations - Working Copy, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Monsour Hospital - Correspondence - Bus. Labor & Political Committees, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - SEIU - Response to Sept. Mailings, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - SEIU - Response to Sept. Mailings Resolution #3, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - PA AFL-CIO - Political Candidate Correspondence, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Trinity Area School District - Petition against SEIU (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Allegheny Labor Council - Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - American Fed. Of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) News Bulletins, 1970-1973 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Allegheny County Government Study Commission - General Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Allegheny Labor Council - Cope - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Beaver County Labor Council - General Correspondence, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Central Westmoreland County - Labor Union Council - List of SEIU in Pittsburgh, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Allegheny County Labor Council - General Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - West Jefferson Hills - Custodians - Contract - Working Copy, 1976-1979 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - West Mifflin - Custodians - Responsibilities and Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - West Mifflin - General Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Westmoreland Intermediate - Agreement with SEIU/General Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Wilkinsburg Cafe Custom Foods - Agreement with SEIU/General Correspondence, 1977-1983 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Wilkinsburg School District - Custodial Maintenance Agreement, 1978-1981 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Washington, City of - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Washington, City of - Contract - Working Copy, 1973-1975 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Washington, City of - Contract, Old, 1970-1973 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Boro of Wilkinsburg - Clerical Correspondence, 1973-1978 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Boro of Wilkinsburg - Clerical Correspondence - Meter Maids, Librarians, etc., 1974-1975 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Boro of Wilkinsburg - Misc., 1974-1975 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Boro of Wilkinsburg - Contract - Working Copy, 1974-1979 (Box 43, Folder 20-22)
  - Wobblie Joe's - Agreement with SEIU, 1978-1980 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Wobblie Joe's - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Gen. Membership & Exec. Board Meeting - Minutes, July 1970-June 1972 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Gen. Membership & Exec. Board Meeting - Minutes, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Executive & Board Membership Meeting - Notes, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Gen. Membership & Exec. Board Meeting - Minutes, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Exec. Board & Membership Meeting - Notes, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Exec. Board & Gen. Mem. Meetings - Official Minutes, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Collecting Sheets, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Quarterly Control Reports, 1974-1977 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Dues Check-Off/Control Reports, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Per Capita Reports, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Exec. Board & Gen. Membership Meeting - Official Minutes, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Dues Check-Off Control Report, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Collecting Sheets, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - SEIU Local 227 - Agreements/General Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Trustee Correspondence, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Petty Cash, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Armstrong County - ULP-C-80-434-W - Correspondence, Labor Relations Case, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Armstrong County - Health Center - Non-Members, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Armstrong County - Decert - General Labor Information, 1980-1983 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Armstrong County - Health Center - Doris Kammerdiener Grievance, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Correspondence - Workers Comp/Natural Gas, 1982-1983 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Food & Beverage Department - Constitutions & By-Laws, 1979-1983 (Box 45, Folder 6-7)
  - Food & Beverage Department - Correspondence, 1978-1982 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Brownsville School District - Decertification - Penn. Labor Relations vs. Brownsville Area S.D., 1983 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - South Butler School District - Cafeteria - General Information, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Staff Meetings - Agenda and Minutes, 1979-1984 (Box 45, Folder 11-13)
  - Brownsville School District - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - United Teachers - 7th Annual Quest 1982 - Conference Materials (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Lifelong Education and Development - Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Solidarity Day - Bus Registration Forms, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Patient's Rights - Constitution & Bylaws of Western Penn. Food and Beverage Council, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - SEIU Local 585 - House Senate Bills - Correspondence regarding Labor Relations, 1976-1977 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Contract Agreement with Conway YMCA, 1981-1984 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Grievance, Harry Carter vs. Allegheny County, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - River City Brass Band - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Correspondence and News, 1977-1984 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Monsour Hospital - Grievance, Beverly R. Beckerleg, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Monsour Hospital - Master - Local 585 Leaflet, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Monsour Hospital - Local 585 Campaign, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Monsour Hospital - Monsour Committee - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Monsour Hospital - Contract Demands, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Monsour Hospital - Florence Williams Correspondence to Nursing Units, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Monsour Hospital - Foundations - Correspondence, Notices, and Bulletins, 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Monsour Hospital - Foundations - Petitions, 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Monsour Hospital - Foundations - Tax Reports, 1971-1975 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Monsour Hospital - Head Nurses - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Monsour Hospital - Correspondence - SEIU to Employees, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Monsour Hospital - Hospital Mailing Lists (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Monsour Hospital - Miscellaneous Name Lists, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Monsour Hospital - Newspaper, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Monsour Hospital - Recognition Requests, 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Monsour Hospital - Telephone Numbers (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Monsour Hospital - ULP Charges, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Monsour Hospital - ULP Round Two, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Monsour Hospital - ULP Round Three, 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Monsour Hospital - Correspondence - Employee Evaluations (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Monsour Hospital - Lucille Anderson Grievance - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Monsour Hospital - NLRB Bargaining Orger Cases, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Monsour Hospital - Unfair Labor Practice Affidavits, 1974-1976 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Monsour Hospital - Correspondence - Contract Negotiations, 1975-1976 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Monsour Hospital - Union Membership Cards, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Monsour Hospital - Official NLRB Report, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Westmoreland County - Gilpin-Grivella Grievance, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Westmoreland County - Cindy Nickolich Grievance, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Westmoreland County - William Trout Grievance, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Westmoreland County - Sick Leave Call-In, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Westmoreland County - CETA Summer Program, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Westmoreland County - Chapter Officers Election, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Westmoreland County - Election Ballots, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 7-8)
  - Westmoreland County - SEIU Applications and Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Jefferson County - Dubois Area - Contract Negotiations, 1977-1979 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Kiski - Contract Negotiations - Working Copy, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Kiski - Contract Negotiations - Working Copy, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Kiski County - Contract Negotiations Correspondence, 1978-1983 (Box 50, Folder 4-5)
  - Kiski - Secretaries - General Information (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Mt. Lebanon School District - Secretary Contract Negotiations - Working Copy, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Mt. Lebanon School District - Contract Agreements and Notifications, 1976-1983 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Mt. Lebanon School District - Cafeteria Contract Agreements, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Point Park - Contract Agreements and Grievances, 1977-1983 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - West Mifflin School District - Contract Negotiations - Working Copy, 1978-1983 (Box 50, Folder 12-14)
  - Wilkinsburg School District - Custodial-Maintenance Agreement, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Elwood City School District - Cafeteria Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Elwood City School District - Cafeteria Contract Agreements - Working Copy, 1975-1981 (Box 51, Folder 2)